Angela Ng Weihan

MA COMPUTING SCIENCE AND MUSIC | UNIVERSITY OF GLASGOW (UNITED KINGDOM)

406 Hyndland House, 10th Keith Street, Glasgow G116QQ, United Kingdom +44 (0) 7842 810051 www.angelangweihan.netlify.app

"Aren't Computing Science and Music really disparate subjects?" I am often asked. Certainly, I find great joy in interdisciplinary studies. I am currently pursuing a Masters in Arts (Undergraduate) at the University of Glasgow, specialising in Computing Sciences and Music Composition. Pursuing my interests in contrasting fields has enabled me to see the interconnectedness of various fields our society and how the knowledge in each of these fields interweave to form a complete whole. In the times I am not found musing with computing and music, I am a photographer, baker and writer by parts. In a nutshell, I most look forward to serving Singaporeans through my career in the future.

Skills and Languages

Web Application Development User Interface (UI) Design Data Analysis Music Composition Team Management English Language Chinese Language Japanese Language

Work Experiences

2020.08 - Current

Business Development Intern

Praxium (Singapore)

- · Delivered campaigns to solidify new opportunities and generate new business.
- · Strategised and implemented successful approaches to revitalise underperforming programmes.
- Networked among local business and community organisations to develop leads and partnerships
- · Collaborated with teammates to develop advertising collateral and sales presentations.

2020.03 - 2020.09

Chief Technology Officer, Co-Founder

Circubox Singapore Ltd. (Singapore)

- Demonstrated ability to simultaneously embrace macro-level strategic decisions and micro-level implementation
- Developed and implemented long-term strategic technological blueprint
- · Facilitated ongoing team development and growth through training and professional skills enhancement
- Maintained high-level knowledge of current and emerging technology development and applications
- · Managed company-level architecture, platform and data configuration processes and protocols
- · Successfully pushed out the Circubox website and Back-End Infrastructure with the team
- · Designed wireframes for mobile application
- Completed the duties of a Director, including but not limited to accounting and document preparations
- · Had partaken in the process of recruitment of staff and volunteers

2019.12 - 2019.12

English-Mandarin Translator

BBC (Glasgow, United Kingdom)

- English-Mandarin translation for a new series
- · Translated both Traditional Chinese and Simplified Chinese
- Developed self-disciple through the remote job with flexible but tight timelines

2019.03 - 2019.05

Research Intern

DSO National Laboratories (Singapore)

- · Completed part of an internship project under the guidance of a Mentor
- · Main computing language used is Python
- Delved into the use of various statistical models in Natural Language Processing
- · Developed independence in research

2016.06 - 2017.06

Education Intern

AIS Cube, Singapore

- Teaching assistant for a Robotics programme for secondary school students
- · Taught students how to assemble motors and coding for the motors
- · Developed confidence in interpersonal skills

Education

2019.09 - Current

Masters in Arts (Undergraduate): Computing Science and Music

University of Glasgow (United Kingdom)

- Excelled in Computing Science with an excellent overall indicative GPA of 21.0
- Excelled in Music Listening through Analysis (music in the long 19th century and Indian music) with an excellent indicative GPA of 21.0
- · Presently on track for First Class Honours
- · Recipient of the University of Glasgow GoAbroad Scholarship
- First Year Representative of the University of Glasgow Student Representative Council
- · Class Representative of the Masters in Arts Year 1 and 2 Music students
- Secretary of the Glasgow University Singapore Society
- · Secretary of the Glasgow Students for Life Society
- Awarded "Hall of Fame" for 502 hours of volunteering in the 2019/20 Academic Year
- RAG Committee Member and Ambassador for the 2019/20 Academic Year
- · COVID-19 Point of Contact for Singaporeans in Glasgow

2017.02 - 2018.10

Singapore-Cambridge A Level Examinations

Eunoia Junior College (Singapore)

- Achieved 3 Distinctions at the Singapore-Cambridge 'A' Level examinations
- · Recipient of the DSTA Junior College Scholarship
- Dean's List for Chinese Language in the 2017 Mid-Year Examinations
- · Student Ambassador of the college
- · Member of the Computing and Robotics Clubs
- Member of the Eunoia Junior College Symphonic Band
- Member of the Python and Machine Learning Circle

2013.01 - 2016.10

Singapore-Cambridge O Level Examinations

Crescent Girls' School (Singapore)

- · Achieved 7 Distinctions at the Singapore-Cambridge 'O' Level examinations
- Top 3 in class for Mathematics from 2013-2016
- · Kangaroo Mathematics Contest Gold Award and Top 5 in Nation
- UNSW Mathematics Competition Distinction Award from 2014-2016
- Singapore and ASEANS Schools Math Olympiad Bronze Award from 2014-2016
- Singapore Mathematical Olympiad Honourable Mention in 2014 and 2016
- Band Coordinator of Crescent Girls' School Symphonic Band from 2015-2016
- Class Vice-Chairperson in 2015